Quratar
By the way, Sherry, you said
you wanted to use a maul,
but do dwarves often use mauls?
Yes.
We may not be tall, but we're strong,
so we're capable of wielding heavy weapons.
I see.
Then let's start by heading
to the weapon shop.
We've been talking about mauls,
but there are all kinds available.
This is the cheapest one.
Identify
Club
Skill Slot
• Empty
That's not so much a club as it is a log.
It looks pretty heavy.
I guess she really is strong.
How is it?
It seems good.
Then that maul is yours.
Are you sure?
Of course.
Thank you.
Quratar, Michio's House
These new leather shoes are for you, Roxanne.
Thank you, Master.
Give Sherry my hand-me-downs.
You're even giving me shoes?
You'll need them since you'll
be going into labyrinths.
Are you okay with just a leather jacket?
It's not like we can get you
a suit of armor to wear.
You're not wrong.
But there are suits of
armor that would fit me.
Sorry.
That's not what I meant.
It's all right, Sherry.
These have nothing to do with
fighting in the labyrinths.
Roxanne, that's counterproductive.
in the Labyrinth of Another World
Harem
Roxanne, could you help
me do our usual thing?
Yes, Master.
We're heading to the labyrinth now.
Would you like to come with us?
The labyrinth? You're going now?
If you can't step away from
whatever you're cooking,
then you don't have to come.
Oh, no. I haven't even started
cooking with fire yet, so it's fine.
By the way, Sherry,
you don't know what empty slots are, do you?
Identify
Club
Skill Slot
• Empty
Empty? Are you talking about skill slots?
You know about those?
There was once someone
who proposed that theory.
According to their theory,
equipment has something called skill slots,
and skill crystals cannot be combined
with items unless they are empty.
Theory? Does that mean it
wasn't confirmed as fact?
Even if skill slots do exist,
nobody can see them.
Actually, there's someone right here who can.
Sherry, what do you think
of the skill slot theory?
I think it's an interesting hypothesis,
but I don't think sufficient evidence
has been presented to believe it.
So Sherry doesn't believe in it.
Well, no matter.
Anyway, I'm surprised you knew about that.
I was interested in the subject.
I once asked an expert about it.
Sorry.
You don't need to apologize.
Oh, right.
By the way, do you know anything
about the Adventurer job?
Yes.
It's a legendary job said to have
been held by the first emperor.
Legendary?
Nobody's seen that job either,
so it's possible it doesn't exist.
So it is a rare job.
Vale Labyrinth, Fifth Floor
I've been steadily leveling up
and can kill fifth floor monsters
with a single blow now.
I need to show off for our new party member.
There they are.
Roxanne, let's go.
Yes, Master.
Watch this, Sherry.
Check out my sick sword skills.
Now, watch this.
See how skillful and marvelous
I am with a blade.
Nailed it.
That was incredible.
Yeah, that's right.
How do you evade their
attacks so magnificently?
She should be watching me.
Watch the monsters closely
and whoosh back when they zip in.
Like I said,
it's a zip and a whoosh.
Don't look at me.
Okay, I've got enough MP.
Let's head home.
Yes, Master.
Teleport.
What's the matter, Sherry?
I've been wondering...
Does the Teleport spell allow you to
travel to places outside labyrinths, too?
And I didn't hear you chant an incantation.
Our Master can use spells and skills
without speaking incantations.
Really?
That's right.
How is that possible?
No, actually...
Come to think of it, you defeated
all the monsters with a single blow.
May I asked what your level is?
I'm level 33.
What?
Master, I thought you were level 20.
I was back then.
Back then?
Even for a level 33,
a single blow shouldn't be possible.
Plus I gain experience points
a hundred times faster than others.
Is it perhaps your sword instead?
I've heard there are incredible
weapons out there.
Well, you know.
Don't tell anyone.
Y-Yes, Master.
So this is dwarven cooking, huh?
It smells good.
I hope you like it.
What are you doing?
Sherry, sit with us.
Are you sure it's all right for me to sit?
Are you going to eat standing?
Can I really eat?
Sherry.
Our Master enjoys eating with us.
Come sit next to me.
Okay.
If I recall correctly,
serving the soup is the master's job.
First, I'll serve myself.
Next I'll serve Sherry
since she made the food.
What's going on?
I feel her eyes boring into my skin.
Here you go, Roxanne.
Thank you, Master.
That was close.
Here's yours, Sherry.
I guess this means I need to
serve the number one slave first.
Thank you.
It's good.
It's delicious.
Thank you.
Come to think of it,
why did you go to the labyrinth earlier,
while we were preparing the bath and cooking?
Preparing a bath is a lot of work.
Weren't you doing it to blow off steam?
That's what you thought I was doing?
You weren't?
No.
I do it to recover MP.
Durandal has the MP Absorption skill.
Come to think of it,
there's something I want to ask you.
Was is it?
Wolfkin have the "Beast Warrior" job
and dwarves have the "Blacksmith" job.
Do humans have a unique job?
Uh...
Um...
I, um...
As long as you'll take good
care of me, I'll be fine.
I'm ready for whatever you
have in store for me, too.
What?
Humans are a species whose desires
sometimes grow to a tremendous size.
So the uniquely human job is...
Sex Maniac.
Sex Maniac?
What's wrong with humans?
Sex Maniac, huh?
In that case, I can't help
but keep multiple slaves.
Come join me once you've undressed.
After all, I'm human.
The three of us are finally bathing together.
I can't even imagine what it's like to bathe
with two women who are there just for me.
I wish I could watch the girls
undress, but Roxanne aside,
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
if I don't want to be called out by
Sherry, I'll just have to deal with it.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
Ms. Roxanne, yours are so big.
Hardly.
But mine are so...
They're very beautiful, even if they're small.
What are those two doing together?
I'm so jealous.
Whoops, I should get the soap ready.
Master.
Excuse us.
I'm also ready to...
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
This is paradise!
This must be a perk—
no, the privilege of being a master.
Sherry, what about your hair bands?
I'll remove them.
You've got a ton of hair.
But...
Once it's wet, there's no problem.
When she's like this, you can tell she's
small and slender, but has a nice body.
Plus her chest isn't so small
that she needs to worry about it.
Shall we start washing?
Yes, Master.
And now Roxanne is standing
right in front of me.
There's a part of her I can't
tear my eyes away from.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
I knew it.
And now Sherry is lamenting her situation.
But I can't help myself.
I feel compelled to reach for them.
This is fantastic.
Thank you.
Okay. You're next, Sherry.
Yes, Master.
Please be gentle.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
She saw how I washed Roxanne.
There's no need to be shy.
Sherry's entire breasts fit in my hands.
Marvelous.
Um, I'm sorry they're so small.
They're not exceptionally small.
That's what I thought when
I lived in my village.
But there were women at the
trading house with large breasts.
And then there's Ms. Roxanne...
Hers are special. And besides,
it's the proportions that matter.
Yours are plenty big considering your height.
You should be confident in yourself.
Thank you.
Sherry, let's wash our master now.
Okay. Um, how?
Like this.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
We'll use our bodies to clean
every last inch of his.
Rather than using brute force,
gently envelop him with the bubbles.
Use your entire body so you
slide into every crevice.
Sherry, could you start on the right side?
U-Um...
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
I'll do my best.
Sure, thanks.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
How's that?
Good.
Thank you.
Okay, let's wash off these
bubbles and get in the bath.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
Yes, Master.
This feels nice.
Totally.
Roxanne on my right.
Sherry on my left.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
Two beautiful women on either
side of me. This is it.
This is every man's dream.
I'm living in luxury now.
This is incredible.
Okay, you two.
Come here.
Yes, Master.
Huh?
Your hair is looking really tidy.
Oh, yes. Soap is incredible.
It's our master's soap, after all.
Sherry, come here.
Yes, Master.
I want you to kiss me before I
go to sleep and after I wake up.
U-Understood.
I've explained our household's rules to her.
Okay, I'm running out of patience.
I can't take it anymore.
It's time to dig in.
Shit.
I forgot about the order.
Roxanne always needs to be first.
S-Since this is what we do
before going to sleep,
as number one, you'll be
the very last one, Roxanne.
Yes, Master. Thank you.
Whew, that was close.
I broke into a different kind of sweat
before we're about to get sweaty.
Master...
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
Thank you.
Sherry.
It's your turn now.
Yes, Master.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
Please take good care of me.
Were you watching the whole time?
Yes.
I was curious to see how
you'd take care of her.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
You can do what you want.
And...
Yes?
Let me know if it's too much for you.
It's all right.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
Go ahead.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm okay.
Please do as you'd like.
Sherry...
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
Sherry, Roxanne...
I can't take it anymore.
Understood.
Go ahead.
Whenever you're ready, Master.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
They're both... amazing.
You worked really hard.
Good girl, Sherry.
Um, is it always this crazy?
I think he was a little excited
today because you were here.
Um...
Yes?
Ms. Roxanne, I look forward
to working with you.
And I look forward to
working with you, Sherry.
Whoa.
Your bedhead is crazy.
Perhaps it's because my hair is lighter now.
The weather's nice again today, Master.
Yeah, it sure is.
Party Job Settings
Kaga Michio
Roxanne
Sherry
Sex Maniac: Lv 1
Effect: Moderate Spirit Increase
Minor Intelligence Increase
Minor MP Increase
Skill: Enhanced Vigor   Abstinence Attack
After all we did, I'm not surprised.
Sex Maniac: Lv 1
Effect: Moderate Spirit Increase
Minor Intelligence Increase
Minor MP Increase
Skill: Enhanced Vigor
Abstinence Attack
The bonuses to Spirit, Intelligence,
and MP will be nice since I use magic.
I can guess what Enhanced Vigor means,
Abstinence Attack
but what's Abstinence Attack?
Is something the matter, Master?
It's nothing.
In any case, now I'm a Sex Maniac, too.
Didn't she say human desires
grow to massive proportions?
Fine, then.
If that's the case, then I'll
let them grow out of control.
Slaves.
What?
I'm gonna buy more slaves.
I'm gonna make myself a harem!
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
I hope she drops dead.
640 thousand nars!
Sold!
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
I hope she drops dead.
Well? Are you enjoying this?
Mr. Michio, would you be willing to take her?
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
I decided to join you, as well.
I hope she drops dead.
But... I could never...
Master.
Please take care of me next.
That's not fair, Ms. Roxanne.
Don't try to steal a march on us.
Let me lick you.
Miria!
Mr. Michio, I could go again.
Rutina?
You just finished.
So good. This isekai is the best.
Roxanne.
Yes, Master.
Sherry.
Yes?
Miria.
Yes, sir.
Vesta.
Yes, Master.
Rutina.
Come on.
Error
Image cannot be displayed.
I'll do all of you at once.
Yes, Master.
in the Labyrinth of Another World
Harem